http://www.popgadget.net/privacy.php

PERIPHERALS
DEVICES (all)
Wonderland
Oh Gizmo!
Our Commitment to Privacy
Your privacy is very important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide
this notice explaining our online information practices and how we treat the
information we collect when you visit our website or register/subscribe to
receive information from us by email. Please read this statement carefully.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on or through
the Popgadget website.
Personal Information
To register for delivery by email of Popgadget updates and sponsored emails,
we require your email address. At your option, additional personal information
may be provided during registration or at other times, if you wish to participate
in surveys or studies conducted by Popgadget. Popgadget does not collect
any personal information that is not expressly provided by you. Popgadget
will not disclose your personal information to any third party without
your consent, except to professional third party service providers necessary
to deliver the services (such as email delivery of issues) you expressly request.
Non-Personal Demographic Information
In connection with registration to receive email updates or at other times,
Popgadget may request optional demographic information such as age, income,
occupation, geography and gender. Such information is used to compile anonymous,
aggregate data not containing any personally identifiable information about
you or other individuals. This aggregate, demographic data may be used to
improve and customize our content to better serve our readers and subscribers,
and may be shared with others, such as advertisers and potential partners
or affiliates of PopLife Media.
Website Usage Information
In addition to personal information and non-personal information as described
above, PopLife Media or our partners or affiliates may collect non-personal,
aggregate data about readers’ usage of our website. This aggregate data
will contain no information personally identifying you or other individuals,
and will only be used to better design our website and services.
Ownership of Information
PopLife Media, LLC is the sole owner of all information collected on this
website.
Registration/Subscription
If you choose to register to receive popgadget updates by email, you will
receive emails containing new stories added to our website. These emails may
contain advertisements. In addition, occasionally, popgadget will deliver
sponsored emails to subscribers, clearly identified as containing sponsored
content from third parties.
Unsubscribe/Opt-Out
If popgadget ever sends you information by email that you did not expressly
request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may request
no future notices.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data sent by a web server and stored on a user’s
browser. Like many websites, popgadget may use cookies to check subscriber
status and preferences. PopLife Media will not use cookies to obtain data
from a computer that is unrelated to our website and services.
Third Party Cookies
Some of our advertisers may use cookies on our website to track information
such as the number of times an advertisement has been viewed (but not personal
identifying information such as user names). PopLife Media may give third
party advertisers permission to set cookies for advertising, but PopLife Media
has no control over or access to such third party cookies.
Links
Popgadget frequently provides links to third party websites; however, we are
not responsible for the content that appears on those sites or the business
or privacy practices of those sites. Please review the privacy policies contained
in linked sites when you leave our website.
Traffic Reports
Popgadget uses industry-standard tracking, which records Internet protocol
(IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP) information,
referrer strings, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. Like most commercial
websites, we use this information in the aggregate to analyze trends, administer
the website, and gather broad demographic information. IP addresses and other
data are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct
use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic,
and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect
online.
Legal Disclaimer
PopLife Media makes every effort to preserve user privacy; however, we may
need to disclose information when required by law.
Changes to Privacy Policy
From time to time, this privacy policy may be modified.
Contact
Should you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please
call us at 301-526-6370 or send us an e-mail at info@popgadget.net.
Back to Top
Best of Popgadget
10.21.2010
We're back!! And where we've been...
Hello! It's been a while, and I'm so happy to say, we are going to be back and better than ever. We will be changing just a little bit- bringing you more frequently updated content, in a somewhat abbreviated...Read More
Popgadget Recent Comments
Popgadget Steals & Deals
Mom Wants Gadgets for Mother's DayTrade-in Your Old ElectronicsPopgadget Giveaway from American Express! My Life on Points6-Foot HDMI cable at $3.19 includes shippingSony offers some exciting deals for Mother's DayUnlocked iPhone! Only $599. Or $699.Got four friends? Take a Peek at this great offerGreen Tech: Eco-fashions priced to move31 ways to save money on technology from PCWorld
Popgadget Random Images
Where is this image from?
See more random images
On This Day
Take a little stroll down memory lane. See what Popgadget was writing about on this day in
This work is licensed under a Creative Commons License | Terms & Conditions | Privacy Notice
